spice2mail.co.in 2014-12-02

# Spice2mail | Get Rs.100 Bonus Get Paid For Reading E-Mail & SMS Ads| Get Free Coupons |Free Online Mobile Recharge

Spice2Mail.co.in is a website owned by Spice Net Media. Wherever the term "Spice2Mail " is used it represents the company Spice Net Media and the services provided through Spice2Mail.co.in. Spice2Mail takes your privacy seriously.  

What This Privacy Policy Covers  

This policy covers how Spice2Mail treats personal information that Spice2Mail collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Spice2Mail products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Spice2Mail does not own or control or to people that Spice2Mail does not employ or manage. In addition, certain Spice2Mail associated companies have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by clicking on the links.

Choices for personal information  

You need a Spice2Mail Account to use Spice2Mail. Spice2Mail asks for some personal information when you create a Spice2Mail Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. A Spice2Mail Account allows you to access services that require registration.  

Information sharing  

Your personal information will not be revealed to anyone outside of Spice2Mail. Spice2Mail employees who get access to this information will be under a confidentiality agreement which will ensure protection of your privacy.

Spice2Mail only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Spice2Mail in the following limited circumstances:

***** We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  
***** We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service , including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Spice2Mail, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Spice2Mail becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will inform you through e-mail before personal information is transferred and may become subject to a different privacy policy.

We will share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, (Aggregate non-personal information" is information that is recorded about users and collected into groups so that it no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user.). Such information does not identify you individually.

Information security  

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to Spice2Mail employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

Data integrity

Spice2Mail processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We reserve the right to check for the accuracy of the information you provided whenever necessary.

Enforcement

Spice2Mail regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or Spice2Mail's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site or by e-mailing to us at [support@spice2mail.co.in](mailto:support@spice2mail.co.in). When we receive complaints at this address, it is Spice2Mail's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Spice2Mail and an individual.

Your choices

You can update your profile information at any time on the Spice2Mail.co.in website.

You can terminate your account at any time. If you terminate your account, your profile, including any messages in your inbox, will be removed from the site and deleted from Spice2Mail servers. Because ofthe way we maintain this service such deletion may not be immediate, and residual copies of your profile information may remain on backup media.

Changes to this policy  

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Policy changes on this page. Your continued use of Spice2Mail constitutes an affirmative acknowledgement by you of the Policy changes. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through e-mail any time at support@spice2mail.co.in
